Goran Vujic

Senior Front End Developer

Aleksandra Ace Simovica 23 Obrenovac, Serbia 11500 (+381) 631293037 goranvuja1133@gmail.com

MAIN SKILLS

AngularJS, ReactJS, NextJS, React Native

SKILLS

- Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ECMA6, Typescript, PHP, Python, Solidity.
- f Libraries: React.js, Redux, Axios.js, jQuery, D3.js, Fabric.js, web3.js.
- frameworks: Gatsby.js, React Native, Vue.js, Vuex, Vuetify, Quasar, Laravel, Django, Node.js, Express.
- 👉 Frontend UI Templates : Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Material-UI, Semantic-UI, Ant Design, Fluent UI
- f Database: MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, SQLite, Firebase
- fracting: Jest, Mocha, Jasmine
- fracking Tools: Jira, Trello
- Version Control : GitHub, Bitbucket
- Server Hosting : AWS, BlueHost, GoDaddy

EXPERIENCE

Simon Property Group, Indianapolis - Senior React Developer

May 2020 - May 2022

- Used React 16.8's new feature Hooks to rewrite/re-factor front-end applications and truncated down 30% codes (better maintenance).
- Migrate code from Svelte to Next.js, React and Typescript.
- Used NextJs for server-side rendering for better performance and for SEO.
- Worked with Lodash libraries for Ajax calls and utility functions respectively.
- Wrote unit tests using Mocha and Jest.
- Implemented Redux Saga's with actions and reducers to implement a sync API calls.
- Assisted in creating a CI/CD pipeline using technologies such as AWS CodeBuild.
- Developed custom Shopify React websites from high fidelity wireframes, including PSDs and Figma using Material UI.
- Worked in developing mobile apps using React Native and its concept.
- Managed shopify project plans for one shopping system.
- 👉 Skills: Next.js / React Native / TypeScript / AWS / Shopify / Material UI / Redux Saga / React Hooks

DELIGHTECK, Singapore - Senior Vue Developer

October 2017 - December 2019

- Developed multiple applications using progressive JS framework VueJS for front-end and Laravel for back-end.
- We developed custom e-commerce shops and websites based on the newest technologies, such as AngularJS, Vue.js, Vuestorefront or Nuxt.js.
- Developed and maintained the major product for the company, refactored the code in PHP Project to Vue project for some major features.
- Implemented modify and design an improved user friendly and efficient UI using Vuetify and Quasar framework for increased customer satisfaction
- Utilized Vue,Vuex,MVC,JavaScript,jQuery,CSS 5,Bootstrap 4,Typescript as Front End, worked in MySQL and MongoDB to deliver new features and fix bugs
- Developed certain features of the application functionality i.e., CRUD (Create, read, update, delete) features using Express JS, Node JS and Firebase.
- 👉 Skills: JavaScript / Angular / Vue / Vuex / Vuetify / Quasar / Nuxt / Express / Node

DATAVISOR, Singapore - Full time Front End Developer

July 2016 - September 2017

- Developed dynamic front-end applications using React, Tailwind CSS, and JavaScript to develop the user interface to validate the user at the client-side and provide responsive feedback.
- Built and deployed jobs in Jenkins for automated deployment in development and QA environments.
- Made use of Redux-Thunk middleware to access Redux application state and dispatched Redux actions.
- Solved Callback in Node.JS by using Promises and Generators from ES6 resulting in unchaining of events and making the code efficient.
- Utilized Bootstrap and to develop a reactive website from a static JavaScript, Node JS, Bootstrap, Semantic UI, RESTful API, jQuery existing code base.
- Extensively used React.js, D3.js, under Score.js, Node.js and lodash.js for JavaScript object and array manipulations.
- Involved in Requirements gathering, Analysis, Design, Development, and Testing of the application using AGILE methodology (SCRUM).
- Skills: JavaScript / Tailwind CSS / React / Redux / Redux-Thunk / Semantic UI / RESTful API

IT ENGINE, Novi Sad - Part time Full Stack Developer

June 2014 - May 2016

- Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.
- Designed and developed web pages using HTML5, DHTML, XHTML, CSS3, Ajax, based on the W3C standards and Web 2.0.
- Created different Carousels using jQuery Carousel, and Accordions with the help of jQuery UI for different product categories.
- Built LAMP stack web applications using MVC PHP frameworks such as Laravel, Codeigniter.

- Implemented and enhanced CRUD operations for the applications using the MVC (Model View Controller) architecture of Laravel framework.
- Performed unit testing and integrated testing for implemented functionality with Jest & PHP to write code faster and improve its quality.
- Skilled in leading frameworks as React.js to build high-quality, scalable and reusable components and Front-end solutions.
- Developed user interface by using the React JS for SPA development.
- Consulting web development for business providing custom software solutions and architecture alongside performance optimization.
- Took initial concepts and managed project plans for one hotel booking system.

Skills: HTML5 / CSS3 / JavaScript / React / Laravel / Jest

EDUCATION

Singapore Institute of Technology - B.Sc. Computer Science

April 2010 - March 2014

CAREER SUMMARY

I'm a freelance Front-end React Developer originally from Serbia, but working remotely in the United States.

I started my developer journey in 2010 when I learned the basics of programming and created my first web application from scratch.

After that I studied multiple courses about modern JavaScript (ES6+), HTML/CSS Flexbox, and CSS Grid on Udemy and YouTube.

In 2013, I joined an intensive full-time web development course in Singapore at Singapore Institute of Technology and completed 800 hours.

I participated in building multiple projects in teams using the latest technologies with primary focus on front-end development, however I'm familiar with Node.js, Express.js, MySQL and REST API.

- Front End Developer with over 7 years of experience in Laravel, React, Vue, Next.
- I have joined 3 enterprise companies and 2 startups during my career and built successful ecommerce websites, admin dashboards, and landing pages.
- Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 80% with improved code and design.

My primary goal is to provide complete satisfaction to my client's expectations with my experience and diligent work.

Thanks for reading my resume.